hostmetro.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy - HostMetro

We are committed to protecting all data that is collected with regard to our clients. When you use our services you agree to the use of that data in accordance with our privacy policy. We in no way collect any personally identifiable information about a visitor when coming to our website unless you choose to provide us that information or as specifically outlined in the privacy policy.

All information collected when you sign up for our services are only done so via SSL secured pages (https) and will be securely stored in our billing system. This may include, but is not limited to, first and last name, address, phone number, email address, dates and types of services purchased, payment method, credit card information, etc. Your financial information will only be used to charge for any products or services that are purchased and can be viewed and modified in your account manager at any time. To access your account manager please visit <https://www.hostmetro.com/login>. All customer information is gathered on a secure server and security measures are in place to aid in preventing the loss or alteration of the information.

We cooperate with all government and law enforcement agencies to enforce and comply with the law. Account information will be disclosed upon valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believes necessary.

Any and all changes to the Privacy Policy will be updated on this page and supersedes the previous version. We suggest and encourage customers to review the Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that it is up to their standards. If, at any time, you feel we are not abiding by this Privacy Policy you can contact us via phone at 800-485-9730 or email customercare@hostmetro.com

© 2020 HostMetro.com. All rights reserved.  
*See terms for complete details. 

Scroll to Top
